From now on, "frog" is me, "sandwich"
means you, and "lemon" means rocket.
(Howard:)So come on, sandwich, build me a lemon
because froggie wants to come home.
(Amy:)Look at you...
(Amy:)...putting on a brave face.
(Penny:)There's nothing to be brave about.
Everything's fine.
(Amy:)Really? I don't know how much
you know about primate behavior...
(Amy:)...but Sheldon's assistant
was clearly courting Leonard.
(Amy:)Were she a mandrill,
she would've bent over...
...and displayed her brightly colored
hindquarters like a big red welcome mat.
(Amy:)By the way, you try that
at the junior prom, you get kicked out.
(Penny:)Okay, maybe she was flirting with him,
but who cares?
(Penny:)I don't even know where
my relationship is with Leonard now.
(Amy:)So says your prefrontal cortex.
But the limbic system of your brain
is calculating...
(Amy:)...that if another woman is attracted
to Leonard...
(Amy:)...it must be because he's desirable.
(Penny:)Well, of course he's desirable.
I mean, he's great.